gohoming.com 2014-06-22

# Your Privacy Rights | Hubzu

Online Privacy Notice   
__Updated March 12, 2012__

This Online Privacy Notice (?Notice") describes how Altisource and its affiliates (?Altisource?, ?us?, ?our? or ?we") collects, uses and shares information from or about you through any online interface (e.g., Website or mobile application) owned and controlled by us (the ?Site?, meaning singularly, jointly and severally, any Website or Websites). We will use and share any information that we collect from or about you in accordance with the Altisource Privacy Notice (above), which provides choices in the use and sharing of information. When using any of our Sites, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Notice. 

Personal Information We Collect Online

"Personal Information" means personally identifiable information such as information you provide, or that others provide to us on your behalf, via forms, surveys, applications or other online fields including but not limited to name, postal or email addresses, telephone, fax or mobile numbers. It includes information we receive from others involved in your transaction, including but not limited to real estate agents, brokers, closing/settlement providers, loan officers, loan sale advisors or lenders. 

How We Use Personal Information   
We may use Personal Information to: 

  * Respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * Send you important information regarding the Site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information;
  * Send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you;
  * Personalize your experience on the Site;
  * Allow you to participate in surveys, sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose Personal Information;
  * Analyze data for our business purposes, such as audits, developing new products, enhancing the Site, improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns; or
  * Control risk, to comply with laws and regulations and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements.

Please see the Altisource Privacy Notice (above) for information on how Personal Information may be shared. 

Other Information We Collect Online

"Other Information" is any information other than Personal Information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as: 

  * Browser information
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies
  * Demographic information and other information provided buy you such as your date of birth; or
  * Aggregated and De-identified Data

How We Collect and Use Other Information

We and our third-party service providers, if any, may record, collect and use Other Information in a variety of ways, including: 

  * Through your browser: Certain information is collected by most browsers, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, device type, screen resolution, operating system version and Internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that the Site functions properly and for security purposes.
  * Use of cookies: Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the device you are using. Cookies we use do not contain or capture unencrypted Personal Information. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Site, pages visited and language preferences. We use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively and to personalize your experience while visiting the Site. We also gather statistical information about the usage of the Site in order to continually improve the design and functionality, to understand how people use the Site and to assist us with resolving questions regarding the Site.   
You can refuse to accept these cookies and most devices and browsers offer their own privacy settings for cookies. You will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser you use. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Site.
  * Use of an analytics and optimization service that tracks and analyzes activity on the Site. We use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, to continually improve the design and functionality and to understand how people use the Site.
  * Use of pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs or other technologies: These may be used in connection with some Site pages and HTML-formatted email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications, the success of our marketing campaigns, compile statistics about usage and response rates and to assist us in resolving customers' questions regarding use of the Site.   

  * IP Address: Your IP Address is a number that is automatically assigned to the device that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. An IP Address is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many websites. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems and administering the Site.
  * Aggregated and De-identified Data: "Aggregated and De-identified Data" is data we may create or compile from various sources, including mouse clicks and movements, scrolling activity and text you type into the Site. This information is used for business purposes, which may include offering products or services, research, marketing or analyzing market trends and other purposes consistent with applicable laws.

Social Media Sites

Altisource provides experiences on social media platforms such as Facebook®, Twitter® and LinkedIn® that enable online sharing and collaboration among users who have registered to use them. Any content you post, such as pictures, information, opinions or any Personal Information that you make available to other participants on these social platforms, is subject to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policies of those platforms. Please refer to them to better understand your rights and obligations with regard to such content. 

Law Enforcement

If required by law, we may provide any and all information we have about you to law enforcement or other government agencies, pursuant to a subpoena, warrant or other order by a court of competent jurisdiction. Where required by applicable law, we will require written documentation of the request, proof of the identity of the law enforcement official making the request, and we will take steps to authenticate the validity of the request. Any law enforcement or government agency request submitted with less than a court-issued order will be evaluated on a case-by-case basis according to the need and urgency, as well as the particular law enforcement agency making the request. 

Links

The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites to which we link. You should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in public forums, such information may be collected by others and may result in receiving unsolicited messages. We strongly encourage you to be aware that when you leave our Site you should read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

Security

To protect Personal Information from unauthorized access and use, we suggest use of security measures. These measures include device safeguards and secured files and buildings. 

Choice / Opt Out

From time to time, we may send you e-mail, e-mail newsletters or Site news updates alerting you to new features, products, promotions or services pertaining to the Site. If you no longer wish to receive these materials from us you may opt-out of receiving them. We will gladly comply with your requests for removal. 

Opt Out Procedure: In compliance with the Can-Spam Act of 2003, on each marketing email transmitted by the Site, there are instructions for opting out of receiving future emails. Such instructions may include, without limitation: (a) clicking a link on the email which sends a reply to the sender's server instructing the server of the sender's desire to opt out of future emails, or (b) instructions for mailing a written request to be removed from future emails. All requests to opt out of future emails will be respected. 

In the future, we may need to change this Notice or the Altisource Privacy Notice. Please review it periodically. All changes will be made here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may share it with anyone. 

Any changes to this Notice will become effective when we post the revised Notice on the Site. Your use of the Site following these revisions acknowledges your receipt of the revision and your agreement to and acceptance of the revised Notice. 

This statement was last updated March 12, 2012.
